FIRLY AFRIANSYAH

Fullstack Developer

Cikarang | +62 856 9517 7537 | firlyafriansyah50@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A Fullstack Developer with 3+ years of experience in Web Apps and Mobile Hybrid Development. Familiar with Javascript & Typescript Programming Language, focusing develop Web Apps and Mobile Apps with React JS and React Native, and able to develop Web Services with Express JS and MySQL as RDBMS. Always interested to learn new programming language and new technology.

EXPERIENCE

PT TOYO INK INDONESIA - Cikarang, Indonesia

Software Engineer (July 2023 - present)

- Execute full software development life cycle (SDLC)
- Develop flowcharts, layouts, and documentation to identify requirements and solutions.
- Troubleshoot, debug, and upgrade existing systems.
- Deploy programs and evaluate user feedback.

Data Analyst - Quality Control (April 2021 - June 2023)

- Have a responsibility to analysis and prepare data to improve quality products
- Ensure all data is well organized and maintained
- Create a data matrix and visualization from results quality check to be reported to superiors

HOMELAB - Bandung, Indonesia

Intern Front End Developer (Mar 2021 - Jun 2021)

- Have a responsibility to develop part of website Homelab
- Slicing web design from Figma using Bootstrap
- Make Website is responsive for mobile

KLINIK SAHBRI FARMA - Batam, Indonesia

Freelance Full Stack Developer (Jan 2021 - Mar 2021)

- Have a responsibility to create and develop Medical Records Apps for Mobile Phone (Android)
- Develop Web Services using Express JS for handling data from Mobile Apps
- Develop Mobile Apps using React Native Framework

CODE MILLENIAL - Karawang, Indonesia

Freelance Mobile Apps Developer (Oct 2020 – Mar 2021)

- Have a responsibility to bug fixing and adjust feature Apps for Mobile Phone (Android)
- Have a responsibility to deploy mobile apps to play store
- Make sure all feature on mobile apps is run as expected

PT ASTRA HONDA MOTOR - Cikarang, Indonesia

Machining Operator (Oct 2018 - Sep 2020)

- Have a responsibility to operate CNC machine for Milling, Drilling, Tapping,
 & Reaming process
- Ensure the products produced according to standards

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS PELITA BANGSA (2019 - 2023)

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering (GPA 3.62)

DICODING ACADEMY (2020 - 2021)

Front-End Web Developer Learning Path (August 2020 – January 2021)

CERTIFICATIONS

- Become a Front-End Web Developer Expert (Dicoding Academy)
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (freeCodeCamp.org)
- React + Redux course (Sololearn)
- Become Linux System Administrator (Dicoding Academy)
- Google Data Analytics (Google Career Certificates)

PROJECTS

- MR Sahbri Farma (Mobile Apps & Web Services)
 (React Native, Express JS, & MySQL) Klinik Sahbri Farma
- Homelab Website (Frontend)
 (HTML & Bootstrap) Homelab
- COA Creator (Web App)
 (React JS) PT Toyo Ink Indonesia
- Quality Control Database System (Web App & Web Services)
 (React JS, Ant Design, Express JS, MySQL) PT Toyo Ink Indonesia
- Competency Matrix System (Web App & Web Services)
 (React JS, Mantine UI, Express JS, MySQL) PT Toyo Ink Indonesia
- Procure System (Web App & Web Services)
 (React Js, Tailwind CSS, Express JS, MySQL)

SKILLS

- Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) & Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- Javascript & Typescript
- React JS & React Native
- Express JS
- MySQL
- Bootstrap, Ant Design, Chakra UI, Tailwind CSS, & Mantine UI